Track 10.1, Unit 10, Vocabulary, Activity 1.
Bài 10.1, Đơn vị 10, Từ vựng, Bài tập 1.
Listen and write the dates.
Nghe và viết các ngày tháng.
What's happening this year?
Năm nay có những sự kiện gì?
Let's write it on here.
Viết vào đây nhé.
Good idea.
Ý hay.
OK, so John's birthday is on the 4th of April.
Được rồi, sinh nhật của John vào ngày 4 tháng Tư.
The 4th! That's right.
Ngày 4! Đúng rồi.
When is his last football match?
Trận bóng đá cuối cùng của bạn ấy khi nào?
It's on the 8th of June.
Vào ngày 8 tháng Sáu.
The 8th of June. OK.
Ngày 8 tháng Sáu. Được.
And the last day of school is on the 12th of July.
Và ngày cuối cùng đi học là ngày 12 tháng Bảy.
Yes, I love the 12th of July.
Vâng, mình thích ngày 12 tháng Bảy.
Our holiday is on the 3rd of August.
Kỳ nghỉ của bọn mình vào ngày 3 tháng Tám.
The 3rd?
Ngày 3?
Yes, and Lily's party is on the 2nd of September.
Vâng, và tiệc của Lily vào ngày 2 tháng Chín.
OK, the 2nd of September.
Được, ngày 2 tháng Chín.
Great!
Tuyệt!